yaledailynews.com 2007-06-16

# Yale Daily News - Privacy

The _Yale Daily News_ , and its advertisers and associates, are deeply committed to protecting the privacy of Internet users. Below is information outlining our support for the responsible management of personal information. 

During the process of delivering web pages and advertisements to you, the _Yale Daily News_ does not collect any personally identifiable information about you such as name, address, phone number, or e-mail address. However, the _Yale Daily News_ does obtain some types of non-personally identifiable information such as the Internet Service Provider you use to connect to the Internet, your browser type, or the type of computer operating system you use (Macintosh or Windows, for example). The information collected by the _Yale Daily News_ is used for the purpose of targeting ads, measuring ad effectiveness, and learning how we can better serve the needs of our users. 

If you would like additional information about the types of non-personally identifiable information that is collected by the _Yale Daily News_ Online please contact us at [privacy@yaledailynews.com](mailto:privacy@yaledailynews.com). 

In some cases, you may voluntarily provide personal information in response to a feature (it may ask you to fill out a survey or provide your zip code). If this does occur, the _Yale Daily News_ may store this information in aggregate form to better understand the type of individuals who view our website. If the information that you volunteer will be used in any non-aggregate form, this will be clearly indicated on the page requesting information.

When you register at YaleDailyNews.com, we ask you to provide your name and email address, a user id and password as well as other personal preferences. After you have registered and sign into myYaleDailyNews.com you are no longer anonymous to us. The Yale Daily News will collect data in aggregate form to provide information to advertisers and other partners. We will not sell or rent personal information to any third party. Yale Daily News will only release personal information about you to third parties under the following conditions: With your consent to share the information; when we respond to subpoenas, court order or legal process; if we find that your actions on our site violate the terms and conditions of use of myYaleDailyNews.

The _Yale Daily News_ Online, as well as most sites on the Internet, use "cookies" to enhance your experience on the web. The _YDN_ cannot use these cookies to personally identify you in any way. What are cookies and why do we use them? A cookie is a unique number that is provided to you the first time you visit our website. This unique number, which is stored in a "cookie file" on your computer, helps us target ads to you, so that you only see relevant advertisements. While we believe that cookies enhance your Internet experience by limiting the number of times you see the same ad and delivering more relevant content to you, they are not required for you to visit the _Yale Daily News_ Online. 

If you do not want the benefit of cookies, there is a simple procedure to manually delete your cookies. Please consult your web browser's Help documentation for more information. 

****  
Some ads which may appear on the _Yale Daily News_ Online website are served and processed by third-party associates. The _Yale Daily News_ has attempted to ensure that only reputable advertising brokers with strong privacy policies may place advertisements on this website. Some advertisers may collect personal information for the purpose of responding to inquiries, others may collect information in aggregate form in order to better understand the needs of the users of this website. Once you have left yaledailynews.com, we cannot ensure your privacy protection and we strongly urge you to investigate the privacy policies of all other websites you visit.

The following statements are required for disclosure of our relationship with third party ad serving affiliates:

FLYCAST NETWORK    
THE _YALE DAILY NEWS_ ONLINE WORKS WITH A THIRD PARTY THAT SERVES SOME ADS TO THIS SITE. TO FIND OUT MORE ABOUT HOW FLYCAST MANAGES THE PRIVACY OF INFORMATION IN CONJUNCTION WITH SERVING ADS ON THIS SITE, PLEASE GO TO [ http://www.flycast.com/about_us/about-privacy.html ](http://www.flycast.com/about_us/about-privacy.html)  
---  
SONAR NETWORK    
"Our Web site uses a reputable third party to serve some of the advertisements that you see on the pages of our Web site. If you would like to know more about the information gathering practices and "opt-out" procedures of our third party ad server, please [ click here](http://www.sonar.com/content/privacy.htm)."   
  
The _Yale Daily News_ Online is committed to protecting your privacy. If you are concerned about your privacy at other sites, we recommend that you investigate their privacy policies. You may also wish to investigate your browser's security and privacy settings, especially relating to "cookie files" and "proxy servers". 

If you have any additional questions about the _Yale Daily News_ Online's dedication to protecting your privacy, please contact us at [ privacy@yaledailynews.com](mailto:privacy@yaledailynews.com).
